const questionList = [
  {
    questionId: 1,
    question: 'Commonly used data types DO NOT include:',
    answerList: ['String', 'Boolean', 'Alerts', 'Numbers'],
    correctAnswer: 'Alerts',
  }, 
  {
    questionId: 2,
    question: 'The condition in an if / else statement is enclosed with _______________.',
    answerList: ['Quotes', 'Curly brackets', 'Parenthesis', 'Square Brackets'],
    correctAnswer: 'Parenthesis',
  }, 
  {
    questionId: 3,
    question: 'Arrays in Javascript can be used to store _______________.',
    answerList: ['Numbers and Strings', 'Other Arrays', 'Booleans', 'All of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
  },
  {
    questionId: 4,
    question: 'String values must be enclosed with _______________ when being assigned to variables.',
    answerList: ['Commas', 'Curly brackets', 'Quotes', 'Parenthesis'],
    correctAnswer: 'Quotes',
  }, 
  {
    questionId: 5,
    question: 'A very useful tool used during development and debugging for printing the content to the debugger is:',
    answerList: ['Javascript', 'Terminal/Bash', 'For Loops', 'console.log'],
    correctAnswer: 'console.log',
  }, 
  {
    questionId: 6,
    question: 'Javascript is an _______ language?',
    answerList: ['Object-Oriented', 'Objected-Based', 'Procedural', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'Object-Oriented',
  },
  {
    questionId: 7,
    question: 'Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?',
    answerList: ['var', 'let', 'const', 'All of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
  },
  {
    questionId: 8,
    question: 'Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript??',
    answerList: ['getElementByid()', 'getElementbyClassName', 'Both A and B', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'Object-Oriented',
  },
  {
    questionId: 9,
    question: 'Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?',
    answerList: ['Throws an error', 'Ignores the statement', 'Gives a warning', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'Object-Oriented',
  },
  {
    questionId: 10,
    question: 'What is the use of the <noscript> tag in Javascript?',
    answerList: ['The content is displayed by non-JS-based browswers', 'Clears all the cookies and cache', 'Both A and B', 'None of the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'The content is displayed by non-JS-based browswers',
  },
]

// https://www.interviewbit.com/javascript-mcq/

